# José Pablo González Poblette

+52 7226079914 chasigamesdev@gmail.com LinkedIn | GitHub

ChasiGames: https://www.instagram.com/chasigames/

With over 5 years of versatile experience in C#, spanning video game and web development, I bring a blend of technical prowess and passion to the table. From crafting immersive 2D/3D games to exploring frameworks like React and Blazor, I thrive in collaborative environments. With leadership, teamwork, and a knack for working under pressure cultivated through 4 Game Jams, I'm ready to dive into new challenges headfirst.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Cube Breaker JAN 2023 – JUN 2023

Mobile Game Development - ChasiGames:

- Designed and developed a full released mobile hyper-casual game using unity.
- Implemented monetization system with advertisements and in-game purchases.

Play Store: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.chasigames.cubebreaker

# Multiplayer - Online Tanks Game

**SEP 2023** 

Created a multiplayer local and online game that consist of battling around with tanks:

- Capacity to host and join available games, either with key or open to everyone.
- Matchmaking implemented to search for an online match.

Link to the game: <a href="https://github.com/PabloGP88/Multiplayer-tanks-game">https://github.com/PabloGP88/Multiplayer-tanks-game</a>

## Omnifood project FEB 2022 – APR 2022

Landing for fake started up called Omnifood.

- HTML
- CSS3

Page: https://inspiring-kataifi-a0b6b8.netlify.app/

Bear Watcher APRIL 2024

Talent-land Guadalajara winner for \$6,000 dollars

- Anomaly detection system implemented with AI.
- Functional dashboard created with React.
- Real time graphs implemented for dashboard.

Link: https://hackathon.genius-arena.com/hackathon/deteccion-de-anomalias-por-analisis-de-trafico-en-la-navegacion-nomaly-sisa/

## **LEADERSHIP & ACTIVITIES**

#### ChasiGames 2022

- Undertook an indie video games studio.
- Mobile 2D/3D game development.

## **ICPC 2022**

Participated in the ICPC 2022 edition:

- Used algorithms and memory management.
- Problem solving and teamwork.

## Representative tennis team 2022 - 2023

Part of the representative tennis team of my school.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Alone Third place winner of Hack n Jam 2022 edition with team "Blopa". DIC 2022

Lead Software team.

Game: https://youtu.be/iuHXBdgYkf0

Capital Quest Second place winner of Hack n Jam 2023 edition. DIC 2023

Lead Software team.

HackMx5 Third place winner of AWS challenge, OCT 2023

Front End Developer

## **RELEVANT SKILLS**

Programming: C#, C++, Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL.

**Technologies**: Unity, .NET, Unreal Engine, Figma, Firebase, Git, GitHub, VS Code, Visual Studio, MySQL, Plastic SCM, OpenGL, React, Blazor.

**Soft-Skills**: Leadership, teamwork, creativity, critical thinking, adaptability, communication.

Languages: Spanish, English

## **EDUCATION**

Tecnológico de Monterrey, Toluca, MX

AUG 2020 - JUN 2024

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Technology:**

Object-Oriented Programming, Data Structures and Algorithms, Software Development, Video Games development and Computers Architecture.